let questions = [
    {
        Number: 1,
        question:"What does HTML stand for? ",
        answer: "A. Hyper Text Markup Language",
        options: [
            "A. Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "B. Home Tool Markup Language",
            "C. Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 2,
        question:"Which HTML5 element defines navigation links?",
        answer: "C. nav",
        options: [
            "A. avigation",
            "B. links",
            "C. nav",
            "D. navigate"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 3,
        question:"var a = []; What does 'typeof a' return?",
        answer: "A. object",
        options: [
            "A. object",
            "B. array",
            "C. string",
            "D. undefined"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 4,
        question:"In what situation should you use the small tag?",
        answer: "B. When you want to add copyright information inside a footer",
        options: [
            "A. When you want to create subheading after a h1 element",
            "B. When you want to add copyright information inside a footer",
            "C. Both situations",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 5,
        question:"If you have a page of search results and want to highlight the search term, what HTML tag would you use?",
        answer: "C. < mark >",
        options: [
            "A. < em >",
            "B. < strong >",
            "C. < mark >",
            "D. < highlight >"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 6,
        question:"How can you print information to the console?",
        answer: "B. console.log(info)",
        options: [
            "A. console(info)",
            "B. console.log(info)",
            "C. print(info)",
            "D. None"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 7,
        question:"Which of the following function removes the last element from an array and returns it?",
        answer: "C. pop()",
        options: [
            "A. push()",
            "B. join()",
            "C. pop()",
            "D. map()"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 8,
        question:"The # symbol specifies that the selector is?",
        answer: "C. id",
        options: [
            "A. class",
            "B. tag",
            "C. id",
            "D. first"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 9,
        question:"How do you call the function 'myFunction'?",
        answer: "C. myFunction()",
        options: [
            "A. myFunction",
            "B. func myFunction()",
            "C. myFunction()",
            "D. None of those"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 10,
        question:"What is not an HTML5 element?",
        answer: "C. blink",
        options: [
            "A. section",
            "B. header",
            "C. blink",
            "D. main"
        ]
    },
]